http://www.stormlake.com/content/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy | The Storm Lake Times
Skip to main content
The Storm Lake Times
SubscribePrivacy PolicyReturn PolicyAdvertiseAboutStaff MembersLogin
Search form
Search
NewsSportsConference StandingsFamily & FriendsBirthday's & Bridal ShowersObituariesOpinionPublic NoticesClassifiedsE-Edition
You are hereSubscribe
Privacy Policy
The Storm Lake Times has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.
Collection of Information
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.
Cookie/Tracking Technology
The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.
Distribution of Information
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
Commitment to Data Security
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.
Privacy Contact Information
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:
By e-mail: webmaster@stormlake.com
By Phone: 1-800-732-4991
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
The Progressive Populist has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.
Collection of Information
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.
Cookie/Tracking Technology
The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.
Distribution of Information
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
Commitment to Data Security
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.
Privacy Contact Information
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:
By e-mail: webmaster@stormlake.com
By Phone: 1-800-732-4991
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
Username *
Password *
Request new password
https://www.willyweather.com/ia/buena-vista-county/storm-lake.html
Tweets by SLTimes
The Storm Lake Times
Copyright 2013-2019 | The Storm Lake Times | All Rights Reserved
220 W Railroad St | PO Box 487 | Storm Lake, IA 50588 | 712.732.4991 | 1.800.732.4992
SSL Certificate
